Viacheslav Nestertsev

Moscow, Moscow City, Russia



slavka2000@mail.ru



linkedin.com/in/viacheslav-nestertsev-a849a3251

Summary

I have been working as a front-end developer for 2 years in the internal development team of OLDI.

I have experience:

- Development of mobile application projects for Android and iOS, web services;
- Development of technical specifications, setting tasks for the development team.
- Development together with the designer of the UX/UI design solutions team.
- Designing and prototyping interfaces for web applications.
- Development of web applications and web sites.
- Development of cross-platform mobile applications (iOS, Andorid).

I am able to build the development process according to the Scrum methodology, I speak English at a high technical level.

I have a basic scientific education in the field of physics.

During his work, he has implemented 4 major projects, a detailed portfolio with a stack and a description of projects on the website https://oldi.dev/

Experience



Junior Software Developer

OLDI.RU

Sep 2021 - Present (1 year 2 months +)

Internal software development team (mobile applications for Android and iOS, web services) in the OLDI group of companies.

- Development of technical specifications, setting tasks for the development team.
- Prioritization of the backlog, tracking tasks in Google Docs, Numbers, Jira.
- Participation in the coordination of the stages of the project (Scrum sprints).
- Development together with the staff designer of the UX/UI design solutions team.
- Designing and prototyping interfaces for web applications.
- Development of web applications and websites.

Development stack: JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, React, React Native, Mobx-state-tree, Axios, Vue.js, PHP, Python, C++.

Key results:

- Participated in the development of 4 projects, all commissioned, a detailed portfolio of projects on the website - https://oldi.dev/
- Implemented a multi-page application for food delivery on React Native (TypeScript) for iOS and Android.
- Developed a business card website for the internal development team (React (JavaScript) + Modxstate-tree).
- Implemented the front part of the B2B equipment sales platform. (The project is still in development).
- Developed individual components of the company's website Oldi.ru and Oldicomputers.ru .

Software Developer Trainee

LLC Fuel Company "EKA"

Sep 2020 - Aug 2021 (1 year)

Internal web services software development team.

- Study and application of modern web development technologies.
- Study of the terms of reference.
- Development of web sites.

Key results:

- Development of a website for internal technical support of ESA gas station operators (TypeScript React + Redux). using the Material UI and Bootstrap components.

Education



Lomonosov Moscow State University (MSU)

Бакалавр, Физика Sep 2018 - Jun 2022

Licenses & Certifications



227008526

Skills

Алгоритмы • ООП • React Native • JavaScript • Git • Mobx • Scrum • JIRA • PHP • Swagger